<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pumpkinella</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2016 20:43:52 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2016 20:43:52 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Beauty Through My Daughter's Eyes</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/beauty-through-my-daughters-eyes-01.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Beauty Through My Daughter's Eyes&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the last few months I’ve been hearing more and more friends and family members telling me I talk myself down too much. They say I’m too harsh about myself and am nothing like the person I seem to think I am. Sadly it was a critique about the things I say about myself and the alarming frequency I say them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t quite know when it started. I guess I wasn’t a pretty child and people made fun of me for being so dark. I also went through puberty at a really young age, way before sex education was taught and so I didn’t develop a particularly positive self-image, being different from all my friends and not understanding why.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I say these things because I’ve noticed my daughter putting herself down lately. At 2.5 years old I’ve started to hear her say she’s not pretty and she’s not the cutey pie I’ve labelled her. The first time I heard her put herself down, it broke my heart. I tried to convince her she was every bit as perfect as I told her and believed she was. However she just got mad and defensive and shouted me down. Any further attempts to calm her down led to tears.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where was this self-deprecating attitude coming from I wondered? But I needn’t have looked very far. I sat down after she’d gone to bed and began to wonder at what point my poor self image had started to rub off on her. To her entire family she is ‘The’ most perfect creature God has ever created. She has a kind heart, an infectious laugh and a beauty as unique and mesmerising as she is. I began to realise just how much of the world she sees through me; how her perceptions are being formed by the attitudes I display around her. We share this really special bond where I can tell what’s in her heart by just spending one on one time with her. When I’m unwell she’s subdued and reflective and when I am well she’s exciteable and adventurous. We have tge bond that is sometimes crippling where we can’t bear to be apart from one another for too long at any one time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She must see in me the fears and self doubts I harbour about myself. She must feel a similar sadness when around me while I’m putting myself down for being the wrong shape, not being worthy of good friendships and ultimately, the one I’m most embarrassed by, not being someone anyone could truly love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My daughter’s behaviour has alot to do with the way I behave around her and the realisation to me that she is growing up with my fears and anxieties is entirely unacceptable. I wish for so much more from her. I need her to grow up breakung any boundaries that stand in her way and truly being an important person for her generation. But in order for her to reach her potential, I must learn to love the person I am, the body I’m in, and the life I’ve ultimately chosen. Only once I can find a way to feel and behave more positively, will my daughter start to adjust her perceptions; seing and envracing her own beauty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I urge anyone that is in a similar position to me to really pay attention to the behaviour you are demonstrating when around your children and indeed even when you are in your own company. Your children are your mirror. They don’t lie or hold back their feelings like you do. They can see through your words, right to your emotions and your intent. They can see the sadness behind the smiles and the look of disbelief when your pay no attention to compliments and kind words from others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am now conscious that my behaviour is not bringing out the best in me and is certainly not demonstrating qualities I want my daughter to feel about herself or I. So day by day I challenge myself to fight through my feelings of fear and insecurity. Everyday provides a fresh challenge, call it an opportunity; unfortunately I fail on most days. But I continue to try, for the sake of myself and my daughter. In order to truly experience love, I must first learn to love myself. Once I can do that honestly, it will be apparent in my behaviour and it too will become infectious. My daughter will soak it all up like a sponge and grow to love and embrace her own unique  awesomeness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope this encourages you to be kinder to yourselves and and love yourself like you want others to love you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/common/brilliant-blog-posts.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Brilliant Blog Posts&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2016 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/parenting/2016/07/27/beauty-through-my-daughters-eyes/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/parenting/2016/07/27/beauty-through-my-daughters-eyes/</guid>
        
        
        <category>parenting</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>From Toddler To Mini Dictator</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/from-toddler-to-mini-dictator-01.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;From Toddler To Mini Dictator&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;its-begun--from-toddler-to-mini-dictator&quot;&gt;It’s begun – from toddler to mini dictator!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pumpkinella is now 2 years and 7 months old and has really come into her own. We can have sensible conversations where we’ll discuss the things she’d like to eat, what games she’d like to play and how her day has gone when I pick her up after returning from work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or fun things she’d like to do during the day. During these conversations I’m amazed at her rate of development. She’s already worked out sarcasm, to my detriment and often makes comments where I’m left wondering which adult she’s learnt them from. In truth I’m embarrassed to say she sounds just like me though so it just makes me laugh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having raved to others that Pumpkinella is such a sweet child and there’s no ‘terrible’ in her 2nd year of life; I’ve recently been sent crashing down to earth with a thud as my daughter has altered her behaviour to make sure she always gets what she wants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of the things often shouted at me are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;‘I WANT IT NOW MUMMY!’&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;‘Go there, GO there…GO THERE MUMMY!’&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;‘I don’t want to eat my food, I WANT AN ICE CREAM CONE/ I WANT CHOCCIE BUTTONS!’&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;‘I DON’T LIKE IT THAT ONE!’&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hopefully you get the gist by now. Pumpkinella knows what she wants, wants it at a specific time of her choosing, and is not afraid to send it back if it isn’t the way she wants it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can just about cope with all of this, well only just! There are two things she’s just recently started doing that have resorted in my bringing out Jo Frost books of techniques for handling toddlers. One thing she has begun to do is to lash out when frustrated. I’ve been accidentally head butted, punched, slapped and kicked during her rare but lethal meltdowns. At first I was in shock and just went along with it to see if ignoring the behaviour would make her snap out of it. However, the behaviour tended to escalate to the point where I’d have to call in reinforcements in the form of Daddy (something I don’t like to do when I’m trying to be the boss-lady).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In comes Jo Frost to the rescue with the ‘naughty corner’ exercise. I can completely understand that it’s not for everyone as it’s very hard work and requires a lot of willpower from the parent(s). Also, Pumpkinella is  2 years old and some might argue that she’s too young to understand what she’s doing. My feeling is that when you have a child asking you if what she’s doing is naughty and then laughing in your face when you say yes, then continuing the behaviour, well you can tell at this point she understands right from wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before resorting to the daughter corner, I try and explain to Pumpkinella that her behaviour is not nice and makes mummy sad. I explain why it makes mummy sad and then tell her about the consequences of not changing her behaviour immediately. If she lashes out because she wants something then she will not get it until her behaviour changes. This works 80% of the time thankfully. She’ll agree with me that it’s not a nice thing that she’s either doing or has done. She will then go a little quiet and start another activity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The point of all of this is that I want to raise a happy and well-adjusted child with a passion for life and will change the world in her own special and awesome way. I dont want to raise a toddler who terrorizes others, lashes out or shouts at people to get her own way. Her mind is developing so quickly at the moment that I understand that much of the behaviour is her just trying to make sense of her environment. She is exercising her newfound independence and understand her boundaries. These will in turn help to further develop her personality and as such can’t really been seen as bad things. Instead, I choose to see this phase as the shaping and reasoning phase requiring guidance, support, and lots of hugs and kisses to help her transition to the other side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank God for &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.netmums.com/&quot;&gt;Netmums&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mumsnet.com/&quot;&gt;Mumsnet&lt;/a&gt;, and other sites that have helped me to see that this is a perfectly normal and excitedly phase in Pumpkinella’s life. Finding the right tools to support her will make sure she flourishes and becomes the gamer-changer I’ve believe she will be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/from-toddler-to-mini-dictator-02.png&quot; alt=&quot;From Toddler To Mini Dictator&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/parenting/2016/07/08/from-toddler-to-mini-dictator/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/parenting/2016/07/08/from-toddler-to-mini-dictator/</guid>
        
        
        <category>parenting</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My In-Laws Are My Tribe</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/my-in-laws-are-my-tribe-01.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;My In-Laws Are My Tribe&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was touched by a story I read this evening about a mother without a village on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://mom.me/baby/31807-moms-without-village/&quot;&gt;mom.me&lt;/a&gt; website&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many of the things in this article resonate with me as a first time mum living in South Wales while my rather large family live in London. I don’t know what I was thinking when I moved away. No, actually I do know what I was thinking. I wanted to learn to look after myself. It felt the mature thing to do, to graduate from university, move out and get a job. Having tasted freedom for a short while during the university years, I was hungry for more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having met my now husband over 5 years on, I was elated to become a parent. But the responsibility and the isolation it came with was unexpected and unwelcome. Entertaining a baby who wanted to be carried and who either slept or cried was a reality I hadn’t been ready for. Without a close network of friends, I found myself alone, without any adult stimulation and my mind slowly turned into jelly with nothing more exciting to say at the end of each day other than to rave about my daughter’s poo’s and how easy or painful breastfeeding was throughout the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I secretly felt that my husband was rather relieved to have a job to go to each day, to get a break away from the stress of being at home. He was very supportive but there were no breaks, no time-outs, not even private loo breaks. Pumpkinella could and would not be without me for any length of time, and I couldn’t bear to leave her to cry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In came the nurturing in-laws. ‘Have you had a bath today?’, ‘Have you eaten today’, ‘What have you had to drink over the last few hours?’. My responses were never very promising so like guardian angels, they flew in to the rescue, taking Pumpkinella from my arms and giving me the space to breathe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As someone normally quite hyperactive, full of life, and child-like, caring for a small child felt like a whole new ball game. I wondered where my friends were when I received no calls or text messages asking about our family’s well-being. It was during the days where I would have a migraine and my in-laws weren’t available that I came to the realisation that it really does take a village to raise a child. Having people you know who you trust not only with your emotions but that can help with the smallest day-to-day things; where were they?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I blamed myself for not being friendly and open enough to make strong enough connections with people who they cared about me even when they didn’t see me. I blamed myself again for being too so far away from my family that it wasn’t practical for them to come and visit regularly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see, the thing is that we all need a village, and a tribe; people that can help to take the pressure off parenting. They can be shoulder to lean on, the reprieve after we’ve had no sleep for 3 days straight, and the voice of reason when we we’re too critical of ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see now why it’s so important to have a network of friends and family close by you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was given a spa day by my colleagues at work to enjoy just before giving birth or in the first months of being a new mum. However, I had no-one to go with and didn’t want to go with my husband as we had no-one to look after Pumpkinella during those early months. I leaned so much on my in-laws that I felt it was too much to ask of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The moral of this story? Reach out to people when you need them. Never take it for granted that they’ll be there when you need them. Take the time to build multiple support systems; friends you can be yourself with; friends that will wipe your tears on a low day but will equally celebrate the seemingly insignificant achievements like the baby’s first spoonful of yoghurt, just to make you happy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, cherish and be gracious for the in-laws who would go to the moon and back for your child, their granddaughter. They love her nearly as much as you do and will be there if you need them. Ask for help, even if it’s just for some adult company and a cup of tea. Don’t expect that these people will know when you need them; but they will always come to the rescue if you ask them to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you Nanny and Tadcu Lewis – you are both awesomely outrageous and we love you to bits!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/my-in-laws-are-my-tribe-02.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Love is... Nanny!&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/my-in-laws-are-my-tribe-03.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Love is... Tadcu!&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2016 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/parenting/2016/05/24/my-in-laws-are-my-tribe/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/parenting/2016/05/24/my-in-laws-are-my-tribe/</guid>
        
        
        <category>parenting</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hand Foot and Mouth Virus in Children</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/hand-foot-and-mouth-virus-in-children-01.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Hand Foot and Mouth Virus in Children&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s actually a viral infection even though that’s what it’s called. It’s not the same as the hand, foot and mouth disease that animals get.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/hand-foot-and-mouth-virus-in-children-02.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Hand Foot and Mouth Virus in Children&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spots, blistering, general redness and soreness are some of the symptoms my beauty girl Pumpkinella endured over the last week. Even inside her mouth on her tongue and her throat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/hand-foot-and-mouth-virus-in-children-03.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Hand Foot and Mouth Virus in Children&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She had spots predominantly on her hands, face and bottom. The most annoying thing about the virus is knowing that I caused it by taking her to see a doctor after over a month of generally feeling unwell. I wanted them to check her over to be sure there wasn’t some other underlying cause why she had been unwell. And I honestly don’t know why I bothered because very rarely do we see a doctor who actually cares.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will always follow my instincts as a mother so when I feel like my baby is unhappy and unwell I do everything in my power to help her to feel better. If I have to take her to the doctors every other day then I will. I’ve also learnt through some life-threatening events to trust my instincts and never just accept a response that doesn’t take into account my daughter’s symptoms, and which supports just waiting and seeing. It’s not that I wish to medicate, rather I want to understand and support my child as best I can.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those of you who haven’t seen or experienced this virus, it’s apparently very common in children under the age of 10. It’s very easily caught through coughing, sneezing, and general contact with fluid from another person with the virus. I am 99% certain that the toy in the doctor’s surgery which my daughter played with was infected with this virus from another sick child. By the time the sores and spots really become visible, the child is already very contagious so it’s a tough one to prevent from being passed on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pumpkinella is rarely in contact with children other than her two cousins, something I do mean to turn around very soon, so I was confident the only place she could have come in contact with the virus was from the doctor’s surgery. She is also a finger-sucker therefore her fingers were a ripe breeding ground from playing with the supposed infected toys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do wonder whether the toys are sterilised or even cleaned each day in an environment that sees illness and infection passing through constantly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be keeping this relatively brief as over the last 2 months I’ve struggled to finish any blog post I’ve started to write. Slowly, its become more and more difficult to write anything I’m proud of so today is my mini welcome back to my passion and favourite pastime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those reading this, please bear with me a while longer till I get back into the groove and my creative spirit is lit again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading and see you soon!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/parenting/2016/04/28/hand-foot-and-mouth-virus-in-children/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/parenting/2016/04/28/hand-foot-and-mouth-virus-in-children/</guid>
        
        
        <category>parenting</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Big is too Big New TV and Telly Addict Toddler</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/how-big-is-too-big-new-tv-and-telly-addict-toddler-01.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;How Big is too Big New TV and Telly Addict Toddler&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been fighting with myself and deliberating over this one for a couple of years now to my husbands great disappointment. We have a 2 year old daughter who’s obsessed with tv shows like &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.studioaka.co.uk/OurWork/heyduggee&quot;&gt;Hey Duggee&lt;/a&gt; (I love this one too), Bing, &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Go_Jetters&quot;&gt;Go Jetters&lt;/a&gt; (great job BBC!) and &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Raa_Raa_the_Noisy_Lion&quot;&gt;Raa Raa The Noisy Lion&lt;/a&gt;. As such we try and keep the tv off as often as we can to give her a chance to play and do other fun things. The thing is though that it’s winter…and it’s cold. I don’t like the cold and I don’t like going to our local parks, beaches or even just taking a stroll when temperatures are in single digits. I just want to cuddle up with a cup of hot chocolate watching corny TV or kids shows with my daughter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So when our 37 inch tv blew up last year, my husband and I had opposing views about what to do. We’d paid for a custom media unit with enough room for a 50 inch tv to be installed but now that we actually had the opportunity to replace it I just looked at my daughter and thought she would NEVER be able tear herself away from the telly if we got a new top of the range one as big as our room could accommodate. However I had found an amazing television from &lt;a href=&quot;http://viera.panasonic.co.uk/4ktv/&quot;&gt;Panasonic&lt;/a&gt; that I wanted. How could I buy it though when I thought about how much time then that my daughter would then spend watching it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Luckily before the arguments begun, our in laws decided they could part with one of the 4 TVs they already had (one in each room). It was a 32 inch Toshiba 1080 so we definitely felt the difference but free is free at the end of the day so we gratefully accepted it. Over the last year though, the longing for one of the new cooler styles has grown. LED, 4K, curved, 3D….the choice seems endless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now as my husband and I absolutely love new gadgets I felt like I had to share with you my budget-busting, bargain hunting road to our new tv. We are still not agreed on the size yet but our in laws, who look after our daughter in the daytime, recently upgraded to a new 43 inch 4K LED  LG tv and my husband hasn’t stopped going on about a new to since.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As our daughter is in theory now already used to a bigger tv my hesitations about how often she spends in front of one have shifted a bit, not to how big it is but simply how long it’s on for. I know my very sensible readers are probably thinking at this point that I should never have focused on size and should always instead have tried to sure my daughter has a balanced and varied routine. So in anticipation of such feedback, and a massive temptation to be able to sit in front of a brand spanking new telly that makes me feel like I’m in a cinema, here’s my lowdown on the best value TVs I’ve found on the market today. They are all suitable for a modest home so any high rollers just think bigger and grander while I bring you my list of practical yet excellent choices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://viera.panasonic.co.uk/4ktv/&quot;&gt;PANASONIC VIERA&lt;/a&gt; TX-48CX350B Smart 3D Ultra HD 4k 48″ LED TV (Found at Curry’s as of 24th Feb 2016&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out at £399 http://viera.panasonic.co.uk/4ktv/ for more information about 4K TVs. I’m totally sold as thy are a superior quality to the normal HD ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/how-big-is-too-big-new-tv-and-telly-addict-toddler-02.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;PANASONIC VIERA&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s such a beauty to behold isn’t it. It’s got free view, the YouTube app and the BBC iPlayer apps pre-installed. It’s also got 3 HDMI ports to connect external speakers and other media.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;PHILIPS 40PUT6400&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out at £349&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;40 inch 4K Ultra HD Smart LED Android TV Freeview HD (Richer sounds as of 23rd Feb 2016)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/how-big-is-too-big-new-tv-and-telly-addict-toddler-03.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;PHILIPS 40PUT6400&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Panasonic TX-65CX410B 65 Inch Smart &lt;a href=&quot;http://viera.panasonic.co.uk/4ktv/&quot;&gt;Viera 4K&lt;/a&gt; 3D TV + HDMI Cable (found at Costco as of 21st Feb 2016 at £529.99)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/how-big-is-too-big-new-tv-and-telly-addict-toddler-04.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Panasonic TX-65CX410B&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This one is a 3D model so I’ve had to factor in buying some more 3D glasses backside toddler + glasses = breakage. I’m not too sure though whether the whole 3D craze hasn’t phased out to be replaced by smart curved versions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So these are my top 3 based on price and quality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought I might need a little more convincing (not so much though) so I also searched for and read several articles about 4K and LED TVs, to satisfy myself that they wouldn’t become yesterday’s news by the time we actually bought one.  I looked for articles online describing their benefits and longevity. This one was quite a fair assessment of the current market and future trends so I definitely think it’s worth a read before taking the leap to buy a new television.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s our before picture to give you an idea of the room and space we have. Hope to see you back soon with an update on the tv of choice and how hopefully our daughter hasn’t broken it or drawn all over it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/how-big-is-too-big-new-tv-and-telly-addict-toddler-05.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Toshiba&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have a great day!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/parenting/2016/02/26/how-big-is-too-big-new-tv-and-telly-addict-toddler/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/parenting/2016/02/26/how-big-is-too-big-new-tv-and-telly-addict-toddler/</guid>
        
        
        <category>parenting</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
